A Guide to the World War I Photographs, 1918-1919
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
{Special Collections, University of Virginia Library}
World War I Photographs, 1918-1919
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
11502
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
The collection is without restrictions.
Scope and Content Information
The collection consists chiefly of panoramic photographs of World War soldiers who trained in Virginia and various aeronautical and medical units.
Contents List
- Headquarters Co., 8th U.S. Infantry, Brest, France / Thompson Illustrograph Co. Petersburg, Va., #7185 n.d. (Folder 1)
- Company K, 316th Infantry, Captain Frederic A. Van Dyke, commanding (#47) Photographer, A.B. Weintraub, Pluto, Pennsylvania n.d. (Folder 1)
- Company L, 342nd Infantry, Camp Grant. Aviation Repair. Captain James B. Kaine, commanding. Photographer, Rockford Illustration Company Depot, Dallas Texas 1917, Nov. 30 (Folder 1)
- 29th Division in a park in Roanoke, Virginia ca. 1918 (Folder 1)
- Signal School, Company 707, Norfolk Naval Base 1918, Jul. 11 (Folder 1)
- 606th regiment of engineers Camp A.A. Humphries, Virginia. Photographer, H.H. Lindsey, Washington, D.C. 1918, Oct. (Folder 1)
- Company C, 130th Machine gun battalion. Photographer, Holladay, Newport News, Virginia 1919, [April] 28 (Folder 1)
- 314th Artillery, Company A. Photographer, Erving, Inc. n.d. (Folder 2)
- Medical officers, Base Hospital, Camp Bowie, Texas. 1918 (Folder 2)
  Scope and Content Information
  Men are numbered and identified by name
- 877th Aero Squadron, Dallas, Texas 1918, Oct. 6 (Folder 2)
- Aviation Repair Depot, Dallas Texas 1919, Jan. 13 (Folder 2)
- Truck Co. No. 5, 1st C.A.P., AEF, Landed Newport News, Virginia 1919, Aug. 4 (Folder 2)